yellowusa.com 2011-01-07

# YellowUSA.com Privacy Policy

### YellowUSA.com Privacy Policy

YellowUSA is committed to protecting online user privacy. To protect your privacy, information we collect is used only in the manner and for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.   
   
**Last updated: August 1, 2006**  
YellowUSA may occassionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will revise the last updated date above.   
   
**What information does YellowUSA gather about me?**  
YellowUSA does not collect any personal information about you unless you explicitly provide it to us. Like most sites, we continuously log general statistics related to visitors (e.g., which sites they came from, the pages they visit, the browsers they use, etc.). This data is not associated to individual users, but rather aggregated for planning purposes to improve our web site.   
   
**What about _cookies_?**  
YellowUSA uses _cookies_ , which are files that store information on a visitor's hard drive. Cookies allow us to customize the site for you and maintain information across multiple pages. (Without cookies, you would have to re-enter your username/password on every page that is restricted to registered members.) The _cookie_ technology we use can not obtain information from your hard drive. For more information about _cookies_ , please see [this site](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie).   
   
**What happens to the information I enter on a form?**  
We may ask for certain information so we can contact you in the future (for example, your e-mail address on the Contact Us form so we can respond to your question). We do not sell or share that information with any outside party, unless you specifically authorize it.   
   
**Do I have to register to use the site?**  
You do not need to register to access the information on the site. However, we do require registration to post reviews of businesses. When you post a review, you may do so anonymously.   
   
**How am I identified when I post a review?**  
We include your first name and state with your review. You may choose to post anonymously and not have that information displayed. However, anonymous reviews do not count towards any promotions or sweepstakes that YellowUSA may have from time to time.   
   
**What about other sites YellowUSA links to?**  
We link to a number of sites belonging to customers and 3rd party vendors. These sites are not under our control. They may have their own privacy policies that are different from YellowUSA's. YellowUSA is not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of any information collected through those sites, and YellowUSA expressly disclaims any liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure.   

For any comments, questions, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
